Translated by Releska
The sky of the blue sea
is so beautiful
I'm going to a day like this
tanto piigata so pipingata
vasueto ni wa tanji to yume o tsutete
mojiro hitsumo ki ni to funging strings
bab dasu, bab dasu,
ara ni yuzumum kamuka ni
saye modonde echan
sou y Jae hapik
so natte kimi to natamanai utara
The time when the light and the light are all connected
You and you, you and you
If you love me, I'll be able to be with you
I'll be able to be with you
It's all thanks to you, Muka Muka!
If I were to test the machine, it would have been amazing!
We did a lot of work in this world!
I don't even know where to go!
But it's not the beginning!
The family of adults and friends seemed to be together,
and I enjoyed this world together with Muka Muka!
Muka Muka!
Let's go!
Muka Muka! Nice catch!
Muka Muka!
Let's go!
Let's take a bit of the ball with us!
You can do it!
I can do it!
Muka Muka!
Huh?
Did you put it in there?
Look for it too, Saritomo!
Yeah!
Where did I put the ball?
It's there!
There it is.
I don't like you...
No no no! I don't like you if I do that!
No no no!
I'm scared!
Hmm...
How do you get out of here?
It's already late, so let's go home.
It's time to go home.
It's too hot.
Let's go home.
What? Is this name right?
Look at this!
Hey, hey...
Let's go!
Don't move!
What's wrong?
Your dad!
What's happening?
Hey, you idiot!
Don't move!
Where are you going?
To the entrance!
Right over there!
Hey, where are you going?
Get out of here!
I'm at an entrance, right now.
Get lost!
No! No! No! No!
Wait! I'll go now!
Hey! Stop it!
No!
I'm scared!
I'm scared.
What was that?
I saw it.
Are you okay?
What?
Oh, my!
No! No! No!
What's wrong with you?
I got bitten.
I'm scared.
What's wrong with you?
Oh!
Oh! It's getting faster.
Why are you crying?
I was really looking forward to it.
I'm scared.
Maybe it's a lady who's holding this knife.
She didn't do it.
I'm not sleepy tonight.
I'm scared because my heart is broken.
I can't get rid of it.
I don't think that's the problem.
What do you think?
I'm scared.
What?
Everyone is scared.
I want to play with you.
It's so strange.
He's so annoying.
He's so annoying that he's so annoying.
Wow!
He's so annoying.
I thought he was a real professional.
I think he's scared.
He's so annoying.
What do you think he's doing?
Don't you think?
It's like she's talking to me like a little boy.
A chance. A chance, a chance, a chance, a chance for a turn.
Make a chance, what's the mission?
There's a good thing. The electric is making a baby with a vacuum suit.
The other two are making a cute little boy play around with a vacuum.
Yes, I will try to make you more difficult.
You do a great job!
You are so strong!
Well then, you guys are changing your mind and fighting!
Yes!
What about the ticket?
The ticket is ready.
Completely activated.
What's going on now?
It does not make sense.
Theхаaahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
Are you really going to the end?
After all...
What the heck have you been doing today?
What is this?
What have you been doing today?
You are planning to go to dusk again.
The
This time, Nokus and Obake came here.
Regisou, do you remember?
It's okay, I love you.
That's the real Obake!
I told you to come here from that place.
So, did you come here to protect your body?
First of all, I wanted to call you to help.
It's so hot.
That's great!
Wait!
Where are you going?
It's so hot.
Obake and I are going to go there.
Obake! Let's go!
I'm going to take care of my brother.
Okay!
Obake!
Mugamuka!
What are you thinking about?
Are you okay, Mugamuka?
Mugamuka!
You're okay, Mugamuka!
I'm okay, Mugamuka!
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
Oh, no! That's a lie.
What?
What's wrong with you?
That's a lie.
Mugamuka!
Mugamuka, calm down!
If you get hit by Obake, you'll get hit by Obake!
But I don't know.
That's right.
Mugamuka!
What?
Did you see us?
That dog?
What?
What did you do?
Before this, Mugamuka came to play with us.
It was a strange situation.
Is there any relationship between you and Obake?
Wait!
You're going to get hit by Obake!
But that's the time!
I'm going to run!
Anyway, we don't want you to get hit by Obake!
I don't want you to get hit by Obake!
It's much more scary than Obake.
Why?
Hey, Mugamuka!
Yeah.
I thought that dog would get hit by Obake.
Huh?
Did you get hit by Obake?
I got hit by Obake.
That's right!
That's why I got hit by Obake!
Huh?
What do you mean?
That's why I got hit by Obake!
That dog is like a dog.
What do you mean by Obake?
I don't know anything about it.
I see.
That dog was Obake's dog.
Oh, my God!
That's why I got hit by Obake's dog.
Mugamuka!
Yeah!
That dog!
If you hit the dog, you're going to get hit by Obake's dog.
Mugamuka!
It's not Mugamuka.
Anyway, I think you should let your dog be replaced by Obake's dog.
I see.
That's right.
Mugamuka!
If you're replaced by Obake's dog,
you'll get hit by Obake's dog.
Right.
I feel like I'm going to see how big and big I am.
Mugamuka!
I'll give a little more power to you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for not knowing you.
Please don't cry.
I'll take care of you.
That's right.
What is this name?
That's a lie.
Please don't cry.
I'll take care of you.
Why did you hit me?
Please don't cry.
I'll take care of you.
Stop it!
What is that?
It's a lie.
What's wrong?
Why did you do that?
Please tell me.
What is this?
Obake has become a black hole.
Obake is trying to be behind someone.
I can't take it.
Obake wants to be with you.
That's right.
There's no white hole in the hole.
Look.
White hole.
I'll give it to you from behind.
I'll give it to you.
What is it?
I...
Please tell me.
I'll give it to you.
When I brought this black hole,
I always put it on my feet.
What?
You're really cute.
Please tell me more.
But why did you become so cute?
Because I always wanted to prank someone.
No one.
If I were you, I wouldn't be like that.
I wouldn't be like that.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
I knew that you really wanted to be with that black hole.
I see.
That's why I put it on my feet.
Obake wanted to be with that black hole.
Yes.
It's really cute and small.
I've been lonely for a long time.
All right.
Let's make a lip balm for Obake.
Really?
Look.
If you do this, you can do it.
It won't be lonely anymore.
What am I supposed to do?
Look.
I'll give it to you.
Yes.
If you do this, I'll give it to you.
I'll give it to you.
Yes.
What's this?
Really?
I brought it for you.
I'm sorry that you were surprised at that time.
Yes.
What's the next Obake?
This is the end.
Yes.
Don't do that.
Please come closer.
Wow.
There's always something in my mind.
I'm here.
Yes.
There's always something in my mind.
It's always my memory of my past.
It's a heart.
Fire, fire, fire, fire, fire, fire.
Let's go.
Go.
Everyone, go.
I'm so happy to be able to see you
Huh? It's Akane's daughter!
So cute! Where's your mother?
My sister!
She was born in the past, so she looks like a baby
She's so cute!
Huh? Are you trying to get rid of her?
Next time on Mugamukapara,
Mugamukana Komoriuta,
look forward to Mugamukana Komoriuta